# Lampson Nguyen – Software Engineer

Oxnard, California - (805) 402 6754 • lampsonnguyen@yahoo.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

I am a Jr. Software Developer whom is passionate about programming and a fast learner. I have experiences with web development, machine learning algorithm, data fusion and data science. With my career begin in Defense and Aerospace industry, I am experienced in Mission Planning software and process, and Electronic Warfare. I currently hold DoD Secret Clearance.

#### **SKILLSET**

~			
C#	C++	Git	
Java	SQL	Agile/Scrum	
Python	VHDL	HTML/CSS/JavaScript	

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

List various lab techniques you have learned through coursework or research. Consider whether this section is relevant to your career or academic goals.

#### WORK EXPERIENCES

# Software Developer at NAWCWD - Point Mugu

August 2016 - Present

Work to support Navy's mission to advance its forces capabilities. Efforts include: supports of FMS in flight testing, and development of business data visualization software, mission planning, and data analysis.

## **RELEVANT PAST PROJECTS**

## Low Level Data Decoding and Data Fusion

November 2017 - Present

Developed a data driven software that process binary data into relational database, utilized SQL Server and Windows Services. Optimizing data processing functionality and data correlation.

#### **Machine Learning Web App**

July 2017 - November 2017

Deployed an image recognition web app that can distinguish different types of vehicle platforms and weapon types. Developed an image recognition web app with Tensorflow and Apache.

#### **Data Dashboard**

August 2016 - February 2017

Designed and deployed static web pages to provide Navy's management the tools and data needed for their business.

# **EDUCATION**

# California State University, Fullerton

Master of Science, Computer Science Bachelor of Science, Computer Engineering *Class of 2021 Class of 2016*